{"name":"New undefined Dataset","interface":{"type":"text_entity_recognition","overlapAllowed":false,"labels":[{"id":"Organization","displayName":"ORG","description":"Edible item."},{"id":"Country","displayName":"CON","description":"Something worn on the head."},{"id":"Person","displayName":"PER"},{"id":"Date","displayName":"DATE"}]},"samples":[{"_id":"s6mg2troc","document":"Ronaldo Luís Nazário de Lima, widely known as Ronaldo, is a retired Brazilian professional footballer who is widely regarded as one of the greatest players of all time. His career spanned from the early 1990s to the late 2010s, playing for top clubs like PSV Eindhoven, Barcelona, Inter Milan, Real Madrid, and AC Milan. He was also a key player for the Brazilian national team, winning two World Cups and numerous other accolades.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":"Ronaldo Luís Nazário de Lima","label":"Person","start":0,"end":28},{"text":"Ronaldo","label":"Person","start":46,"end":53},{"text":" 1990","label":"Date","start":202,"end":207},{"text":" 2010","label":"Date","start":220,"end":225},{"text":"PSV Eindhoven","label":"Organization","start":255,"end":268},{"text":"Barcelona","label":"Organization","start":270,"end":279},{"text":"Inter Milan","label":"Organization","start":281,"end":292},{"text":"Real Madrid","label":"Organization","start":294,"end":305},{"text":"AC Milan","label":"Organization","start":311,"end":319},{"text":"Brazilian national team","label":"Organization","start":354,"end":377}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"szltelbqa","document":"Early Career and Breakthrough:","annotation":{"entities":[]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"s4r0h077b","document":"Ronaldo began his professional career at Cruzeiro in Brazil, where he quickly gained attention for his incredible speed, dribbling skills, and goal-scoring ability.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":"Ronaldo","label":"Person","start":0,"end":7},{"text":"Cruzeiro","label":"Organization","start":41,"end":49},{"text":"Brazil","label":"Country","start":53,"end":59}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"sd1x7ms1k","document":"In 1994, he moved to PSV Eindhoven in the Netherlands, where he continued to impress, scoring 54 goals in 57 matches.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":" 1994, ","label":"Date","start":2,"end":9},{"text":"PSV Eindhoven","label":"Organization","start":21,"end":34},{"text":"Netherlands","label":"Country","start":42,"end":53}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"siijjh5ec","document":"His performances earned him a move to Barcelona for the 1996-97 season, where he scored 47 goals in 49 games, winning the European Golden Shoe.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":"Barcelona","label":"Organization","start":38,"end":47},{"text":" 1996-97 ","label":"Date","start":55,"end":64}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"sfsdiz5vs","document":"Dominance in Europe:","annotation":{"entities":[]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"su8vj8hdi","document":"After Barcelona, Ronaldo joined Inter Milan in 1997 for a then-world record fee.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":"Barcelona","label":"Organization","start":6,"end":15},{"text":"Ronaldo","label":"Person","start":17,"end":24},{"text":"Inter Milan","label":"Organization","start":32,"end":43},{"text":" 1997 ","label":"Date","start":46,"end":52}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"seyy3jpo4","document":"He became known as \"Il Fenomeno\" (The Phenomenon) for his dazzling displays of skill, power, and finishing.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":"Il Fenomeno","label":"Person","start":20,"end":31}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"s2y8yftnr","document":"Ronaldo won the Ballon d'Or in 1997 and 2002, and the FIFA World Player of the Year award three times (1996, 1997, and 2002).","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":"Ronaldo","label":"Person","start":0,"end":7},{"text":" 1997 ","label":"Date","start":30,"end":36},{"text":" 2002, ","label":"Date","start":39,"end":46},{"text":" (1996, 1997, ","label":"Date","start":101,"end":115},{"text":" 2002).","label":"Date","start":118,"end":125}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"slcgwsvzc","document":"He also won the UEFA Cup with Inter in 1998.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":" 1998.","label":"Date","start":38,"end":44}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"s2i3f03c9","document":"Injuries and Comeback:","annotation":{"entities":[]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"srwtg8w5y","document":"Ronaldo suffered a series of serious knee injuries throughout his career, including two major setbacks during his time at Real Madrid.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":"Ronaldo","label":"Person","start":0,"end":7},{"text":"Real Madrid","label":"Organization","start":122,"end":133}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"sh48fdxgr","document":"Despite these challenges, he made remarkable comebacks, demonstrating his resilience and determination.","annotation":{"entities":[]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"s0q5npjyu","document":"Return to Brazil and Retirement:","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":"Brazil","label":"Country","start":10,"end":16}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"s2rrprb2n","document":"After playing for Real Madrid and AC Milan, Ronaldo returned to Brazil to play for Corinthians.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":"Real Madrid","label":"Organization","start":18,"end":29},{"text":"AC Milan","label":"Organization","start":34,"end":42},{"text":"Ronaldo","label":"Person","start":44,"end":51},{"text":"Brazil","label":"Country","start":64,"end":70},{"text":"Corinthians","label":"Organization","start":83,"end":94}]},"brush":"complete"},{"_id":"s2y66lgfc","document":"He retired from professional football in 2011.","annotation":{"entities":[{"text":" 2011.","label":"Date","start":40,"end":46}]},"brush":"complete"}]}